# Navin Choukse

#### Contact

Location Open to all Locations

Joining -Immediately

DOB

01/01/1987

**Phone** 

+91-9926812292

E-mail

navinchouksey111@yahoo.co.in

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/navin-choukse-36565756

## **Skills**

ATL, BTL & TTL Activity

Social media campaign

Campaign management,
Promotional Planning

Media & Vendor Relationship

Marketing, Branding and Advertising

Mobile Marketing, Event networking

Over 11 Years of experience in performance-driven marketing professional skilled in creating marketing plans and leading successful Digital Marketing, product launches, promotions, and development. Well-versed in SEO content creation, social media audience engagement and brand management, public relations, and online promotions. Fiscally responsible in monitoring budgets by comparing and analyzing actual results with plans and forecasts.

# **Work History**

2023-08 current

## **Marketing Manager**

K & D Engineering

- Responsible for Planning and execute ATL, BTL, TTL marketing activities. Offline campaigns, Digital marketing activities, making content calendar for digital activities and handle the digital agencies
- Handle the team for the marketing and agencies for the marketing activities.
- Planned and executed offline campaigns across different channels like manufactures companies, automotives, plant engineers, Textiles etc.
- Worked with different payroll partners for staffing and payroll

**Skills:** Brand Awareness · Marketing · Project Management · B2B Marketing, Marketing Strategy.

2023-02 – 2023-07

## **Marketing Manager**

Byju's., Pune

- Campaign Management, Advertising, Data analysis, Marketing Strategy, Project management, google analytic, SEO, SEM.
- Responsible for planning and execution of BTL
  Offline Campaigns, School Contact Programs,
  building new marketing alliances, vendor
  management and coordination with internal and
  external stakeholders for various marketing
  initiatives.

- Led a team of 4 Managers, 32 Assistant Managers, 18 Team Leaders and 600+ Executives worked at different subfunction and ensured end-to-end delivery for different product segments like BYJU'S NEO Classes, BYJU'S Tuition Center, Aakash BYJU'S, BYJU'S Tablet Learning Program, Disney BYJU'S Early Learn and WhiteHat Jr
- Planned and executed offline campaigns across different channels like Malls, Retail Chains, RWAs, Hypermarkets, Supermarkets, Movie Theatres, and Feet on Street.
- Worked with different payroll partners for staffing and payroll

**Skills**: Brand Awareness · Marketing · Project Management · B2B Marketing · Business Development · Marketing Strategy

#### 2019-01 – 2023-01

#### **Lead Marketer**

Landmark Cars Ltd., Indore

- Campaign Management, Advertising, Data analysis, Marketing Strategy, Project management, google analytic, SEO, SEM. Email Marketing & Social media Marketing,
- Managed marketing budget and associated P&L to develop and execute marketing strategies, budgets, and sales plans for business segments.
- Planned, implemented, and tracked sales and marketing strategies to promote brand products.
- Improved and boosted brand image by implementing focused marketing campaigns and engaging in professional networking to support outreach.
- Planned marketing initiatives and leveraged referral networks to promote business development.
- Updated social media platforms with latest news and corporate details.
- Created company brand messaging, collateral

- materials, customer events, promotional strategies, and product commercialization.
- Generated reports detailing campaign performance, customer engagement and engagement trends.

2018-03 -2019-01

#### **Senior Marketing Executive**

Asian Granito India Ltd (AGL Tiles)., Indore

- Developed marketing plans based upon extensive research and prospects targeted and promote brand image of AGL in order to increase market share and sales.
- Developed and recommended customer centric product positioning to increase sales.
- Developed and implemented B2B marketing strategy and overall communication plans to produce long-term partners.
- Cultivated and maintained strategic alliances with key partners and vendors.
- Managed production of leaflets, posters, and newsletters.

2015-06 - Assistant Marketing Manager

Landmark Cars Ltd., Indore

2012-07 - **Executive** 2014-06

UJAAS Energy LTD., Indore

## **Education**

2012-07 - MBA: Marketing and HR

2014-06 DAVV - Indore

2009-07 - Bachelor of commerce: Accounting and 2012-04

# **Computer Science**

DAVV - Indore

# **Personal Details**

Father's

Late Mr. Dilip Choukse

Name

DOB

01/01/1987

Hobbies

Watching Movies, Traveling, Exercise

Permanent

Address.

F-50/I, Lav-Kush Sukhliya, Indore

**Navin Choukse**